{
   "quiz_1": [
      {
         "question_type":"mc",
         "question_text":"What HTML tag is used to embed an image in an HTML page?",
         "question_options":[
            "table",
            "img",
            "head",
            "body"
         ],
         "correct_answer":"img",
         "answer_explanation":"<img> is the correct tag used for dealing with image embeds."
      },
      {
         "question_type":"text",
         "question_text":"In Java, the index of an array starts at ___.",
         "answer_field":"text_answer",
         "correct_answer":"0",
         "answer_explanation":"The index of an array always starts at 0 when working with Java, due to how the compiler works."
      },
      {
         "question_type":"tf",
         "question_text":"The <img> tag does not require a closing tag.",
         "question_options":[
            "True",
            "False"
         ],
         "correct_answer":"True",
         "answer_explanation":"img is a special tag, so you can just use a / on the opening tag if there is no closing tag. Ex. <img src=... />"
      },
      {
         "question_type":"tf",
         "question_text":"Java is a statically typed language.",
         "question_options":[
            "True",
            "False"
         ],
         "correct_answer":"True",
         "answer_explanation":"Java is a statically typed language, meaning you MUST declare the variable type before assigning a value e.g. \"int x = 5\""
      },
      {
         "question_type":"mc",
         "question_text":"Which HTML tag defines a table row?",
         "question_options":[
            "th",
            "table",
            "tr",
            "td"
         ],
         "correct_answer":"tr",
         "answer_explanation":"<tr> is used to specify how many rows a table has."
      },
      {
         "question_type":"mc",
         "question_text":"Handlebars is an example of an _____ engine.",
         "question_options":[
            "motor",
            "templating",
            "identity",
            "isotope"
         ],
         "correct_answer":"templating",
         "answer_explanation":"Templating engines utilize a different syntax that replaces placeholders to assist on the front-end and back-end."
      },
      {
         "question_type":"tf",
         "question_text":"HTML tags are case-sensitive",
         "question_options":[
            "True",
            "False"
         ],
         "correct_answer":"False",
         "answer_explanation":"It is not required, but it is recommended to make your HTML tags lowercase, and is even demanded from stricter document types like XHTML. Ex. <P> means the same as <p>"
      },
      {
         "question_type":"tf",
         "question_text":"\\:https://www.google.com/\\: is an absolute URL.",
         "question_options":[
            "True",
            "False"
         ],
         "correct_answer":"True",
         "answer_explanation":"Absolute URLs link to something that is hosted on another website."
      },
      {
         "question_type":"mc",
         "question_text":"What language is Bootstrap for?",
         "question_options":[
            "HTML",
            "CSS",
            "JavaScript",
            "JSON"
         ],
         "correct_answer":"CSS",
         "answer_explanation":"Bootstrap is used to help streamline CSS."
      },
      {
         "question_type":"mc",
         "question_text":"What is the head tag used for?",
         "question_options":[
            "Important info that should be displayed at the top of the web browser",
            "Information that isn't rendered on the web browser",
            "Content that is to be rendered or displayed on the browser window",
            "Info that should be displayed at the bottom of the web browser"
         ],
         "correct_answer":"Information that isn't rendered on the web browser",
         "answer_explanation":"The head tag provides info to the browser on how to load the page + additional resources"
      },
      {
         "question_type":"mc",
         "question_text":"What is the body tag used for?",
         "question_options":[
            "Important info that should be displayed at the top of the web browser",
            "Information that isn't rendered on the web browser",
            "Content that is to be rendered or displayed on the browser window",
            "Info that should be displayed at the bottom of the web browser"
         ],
         "correct_answer":"Content that is to be rendered or displayed on the browser window",
         "answer_explanation":"The information within the body tag is what's parsed and rendered."
      },
      {
         "question_type":"mc",
         "question_text":"The src attribute _______.",
         "question_options":[
            "specifies the URL of the page that the link goes to",
            "specifies an alternate text for an image",
            "specifies the path to the image to be displayed",
            "specifies the height of an image"
         ],
         "correct_answer":"specifies the path to the image to be displayed",
         "answer_explanation":"It is commonly used in the <img> tag."
      },
      {
         "question_type":"tf",
         "question_text":"HTML is a programming language.",
         "question_options":[
            "True",
            "False"
         ],
         "correct_answer":"False",
         "answer_explanation":"HTML stands for HyperText Markup Language, so HTML is a markup language."
      },
      {
         "question_type":"tf",
         "question_text":"The script tag is used for JavaScript.",
         "question_options":[
            "True",
            "False"
         ],
         "correct_answer":"True",
         "answer_explanation":"<script> is used in an html file whereever there are JavaScript snippets."
      },
      {
         "question_type":"mc",
         "question_text":"<____> defines a list with bullet points.",
         "question_options":[
            "ol",
            "al",
            "ul",
            "li"
         ],
         "correct_answer":"ul",
         "answer_explanation":"<ul> defines an unordered list."
      },
      {
         "question_type":"mc",
         "question_text":"<____> defines a list with numbers.",
         "question_options":[
            "ol",
            "al",
            "ul",
            "li"
         ],
         "correct_answer":"ol",
         "answer_explanation":"<ol> defines an ordered list."
      },
      {
         "question_type":"mc",
         "question_text":"The href attribute _______.",
         "question_options":[
            "specifies the URL of the page that the link goes to",
            "specifies an alternate text for an image",
            "specifies the path to the image to be displayed",
            "specifies the height of an image"
         ],
         "correct_answer":"specifies the URL of the page that the link goes to",
         "answer_explanation":"It is used in tags like <a>, which are used to define hyperlinks."
      },
      {
         "question_type":"mc",
         "question_text":"The alt attribute _______.",
         "question_options":[
            "specifies the URL of the page that the link goes to",
            "specifies an alternate text for an image",
            "specifies the path to the image to be displayed",
            "specifies the height of an image"
         ],
         "correct_answer":"specifies an alternate text for an image",
         "answer_explanation":"The alt attribute is handy for when an image cannot be displayed for some reason"
      },
      {
         "question_type":"mc",
         "question_text":"For the target tag, which attribute opens the document in a parent frame?",
         "question_options":[
            "parent",
            "self",
            "blank",
            "top"
         ],
         "correct_answer":"parent",
         "answer_explanation":"target= \"parent\" opens the document in a parent frame."
      },
      {
         "question_type":"mc",
         "question_text":"The height attribute _______.",
         "question_options":[
            "specifies the URL of the page that the link goes to",
            "specifies an alternate text for an image if the image cannot be displayed for some reason",
            "specifies the path to the image to be displayed",
            "specifies the height of an image"
         ],
         "correct_answer":"specifies the height of an image",
         "answer_explanation":"The width and height attributes can be in either percentages or pixels."
      }
   ]
}
